(Sheldon:)My mother warned me this is what happens
to pretty boys in the big city.
(Penny:)No, we just want information.
(Sheldon:)Oh. Oh, I've got that in spades. Ravage me.
(Penny:)We heard you read the letter
from Howard's father.
(Bernadette:)- I did.
- What did it say?
(Sheldon:)I can't tell you that.
I'm bound by closet organizer-organizee
confidentiality.
(Amy:)Sheldon, that's not a real thing.
(Sheldon:)Neither is the rule that you have to hold
your girlfriend's hand at the movies.
But that doesn't stop you
from pawing at me...
(Sheldon:)...like you're a bear
and I'm a trash can full of sweets.
(Penny:)Why do you even care?
Just tell us what it says.
(Sheldon:)Control over the information
contained in that letter belongs to Howard.
(Sheldon:)By happenstance, I came to know it.
(Sheldon:)That doesn't give me the right
to disseminate it freely.
(Penny:)The letter was found in Bernadette's closet.
Doesn't that count for something?
(Sheldon:)Are you pointing out that California
is a community-property state...